

# **JEFFERSON ARIAS ZUÑIGA**

Junior Frontend Developer

**1** 317 5424168

yeton@jesuslife12.com

**P** cc 1006168992

## **PROFILE**

I'm Jefferson Arias, a proactive frontend Flutter development student with a focus on creating unique and innovative digital experiences. My interest in technology and programming led me to explore the world of web and mobile development, and since then, I have been learning and perfecting my skills in this field.

## **EXPERIENCE**

2019 - 2021 Web Developer Jesuslife12

2021 - 2023 **LVP Proplayer** 

ELR Gaming -Skull Cracker

### **EDUCATION**

**PROM 2016 BACHILLER TECNICO INDUSTRIAL** 

I.E.T.I José María Carbonell

2014 - 2016 **TECNICO EN SISTEMAS** 

SENA: Servicio Nacional De Aprendizaje

2016

**ENGLISH DOT WORKS** 

SENA: Servicio Nacional De Aprendizaje

## **SKILLS**

- Teamwork
- Comunication
- Proactivitie
- Creativity
- learnability
- Effectiveness

## REFERENCES

#### CAMPO ELIAS GÚZMAN

CEO of Jesuslife12 +1 (786) 354-1162 campo@jesuslife12.com

#### **BRAYAN CASTAÑO**

Manager at ELR working and Gaming 315 9277019 ELR\_Gaming@gmail.com